<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Reuben Francis</title>
    <link>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Reuben Francis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://reubenbf.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizing YOLOv4-tiny</title>
      <link>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-5/</guid>
      <description>🎨 Hugely inspired by roboflow-ai and The AI Guy
 📝 Prerequisites  Preprocess your labelled dataset for free on roboflow it&amp;rsquo;s easier. Downloading pre-trained weights for faster training ⏩ Time ⏲, your models can take quite some time to train, get a snack, or some sleep while it&amp;rsquo;s at it.  Image Annotation Optionally, you can use LabelImg to label your images from scratch.
👀 Usage Just follow the steps mentioned in the notebook and get started 😬.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NowPlay-Box</title>
      <link>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-4/</guid>
      <description>📌✨ For more pinned-gist projects like this one, check out: https://github.com/matchai/awesome-pinned-gists
  Project hugely inspired by https://github.com/RangerDigital/neko-box
  NowPlay-Box is a simple GitHub Action built to make dynamic Gist displaying the album you&amp;rsquo;re now-playing on Spotify .
 Usage To start, you need to prepare some things:
  Create a new public GitHub Gist at https://gist.github.com/
  Create an Access Token with the gist scope and save it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple VGG 16 Classifier</title>
      <link>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-6/</guid>
      <description> Simple VGG16 classifier using Keras and Streamlit
 Requirements Python 3.x with all requirements.txt dependencies installed. To install run:
$ git clone https://github.com/reubenbf/simple-vgg-classifier.git$ cd ./simple-vgg-classifier/$ pip install -r requirements.txt Get the Classifier Running Make sure to have the images you need to classify in the ./images directory
$ cp /path/to/image/ ./images  Get the data app running
$ streamlit run upload.py Results </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Music Activity Analysis</title>
      <link>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-1/</guid>
      <description>The project explores personal music activity, using Last.fm, a website that builds a detailed profile of each user&amp;rsquo;s musical taste by recording details of the tracks heard by the user and RateYourMusic a collaborative music database used to catalog and rate music (and films). The former however has a &amp;lsquo;Report&amp;rsquo; section that does statistically create reports for past week and year but is quite limited. We use the liberty of having the overall archival data of both the websites to have the ability to visualize overall, yearly, monthly, weekly or even daily stats for artists, their albums, ratings per album or even play counts and various other combinations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellenous Portfolios</title>
      <link>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-3/</guid>
      <description>These Data Science portfolios explore the sklearn package and realizes simple analytical understanding on various data. Each of these projects shows how the data looks like, with visualizations and models created to further understand undelying insights.
Projects   Analysis of CSV data for cycling 
  Analysing COVID-19 Data 
  Predicting the Genre of Books from Summaries 
  Links Link to GitHub Repository
DATASET present in .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reproducibility Project: Simple Scenery Image Classification and Neural Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reubenbf.github.io/project/project-2/</guid>
      <description>We look at original works (Image Classification using Conventional models and Neural Style Transfer) and prove it&amp;rsquo;s reprodicibiity by replicating them. we first create a few conventional models to classify a certain dataset, secondly create a neural style transfer model that stylestically change an image from the same dataset and finally compare these images back to the conventional models to notice if the model can still classify them correctly
Dataset We use the “8 Scene Categories Dataset” taken from Aude Oliva, Antonio Torralba’s study] that contains eight outdoor scene categories: coast, mountain, forest, open country, street, inside city, tall buildings and highways.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>